{"data":[{"question":"According to a recent survey, ________ doctors do not have a personal physician.","a":"a large amount of","b":"large amount of","c":"a large number of","d":"large number of","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A large\/considerable etc amount of something: used to talk about how much there is of a feeling or quality.\u00a0\n- A large number of: + Countable plural noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"There are many beautifully preserved historic buildings ________.","a":"in Beacon street in Boston","b":"in Beacon street at Boston","c":"on Beacon street in Boston","d":"at Beacon street on Boston","answer":"3","explain":"\n- On: + street name.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"The prime rate is the rate of interest that a bank will charge when it ________ money to its best clients.","a":"lent","b":"borrows","c":"borrowed","d":"lends","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Lend something to somebody = lend somebody something\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"The area where a microchip is manufactured must be the ________ environment possible.","a":"most cleanest","b":"cleanest","c":"more cleanest","d":"cleaner","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the superlative form of short adjective (clean)\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Mathematics is ________ and serves so many of the sciences that it is a prerequisite for studying every scientific discipline.","a":"such important field","b":"such an important field","c":"such a important field","d":"so an important field","answer":"2","explain":"\n- So\/such...that: used when emphasizing the degree or amount of something by saying what the result is.\u00a0\n+ So + adj + that.\u00a0\n+ Such + noun phrase (adj + noun).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Studies of job satisfaction are unreliable because there ________. So many variables and because the admission of dissatisfaction may be viewed as a personal failure.","a":"was","b":"were","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The words\u00a0here and there have generally been labeled as adverbs even though they indicate place. In sentences beginning with here or there, the subject follows the verb.\n\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"I knew I could rely ________ them to get the job done.","a":"in","b":"with","c":"of","d":"on","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Rely on\/upon somebody\/something: to trust or depend on someone or something to do what you need or expect them to do.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Champlain founded a base at port royal in 1605, and ________ a fort at Quebec three years later.","a":"builds","b":"built","c":"to built","d":"building","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the parallel structure with past form of verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Natural gas often occurs together ________ petroleum in the minute pores of rocks such as sandstone and limestone.","a":"with","b":"in","c":"by","d":"along","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Together with something\/somebody: in addition to something else.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"There is no limit to the diversity to be ________ in the cultures of people throughout the world.","a":"finding","b":"found","c":"find","d":"to find","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To be + Past participle: the passive voice","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"}]}